<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<text>
	<title>Come, Thou Fount of Every Blessing</title>
	<author>Robert Robinson</author>
	<year>1758</year>
	<meter name="null">
		<count>15</count>
		<count>15</count>
		<count>15</count>
		<count>15</count>
	</meter>
	<verses>
		<verse>
			<line>Come, Thou Fount of e- very bless- ing, tune my heart to sing Thy grace; </line>
			<line>Streams of mer- cy, nev- er ceas- ing, call for songs of loud- est praise. </line>
			<line>Teach me some me- lo- dious son- net, sung by flam- ing tongues ab- ove. </line>
			<line>Praise the mount! I'm fixed up- on it, mount of Thy re- deem- ing love. </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>Sorrow- ing I shall be in spi- rit, till re- leased from flesh and sin, </line>
			<line>Yet from what I do in- he- rit, here Thy prai- ses I'll be- gin; </line>
			<line>Here I raise my Eb- en- e- zer; here by Thy great help I've come; </line>
			<line>And I hope, by Thy good plea- sure, safe- ly to a- rrive at home. </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>Je- sus sought me when a stran- ger, wand- ring from the fold of God; </line>
			<line>He, to res- cue me from dan- ger, in- ter- posed His pre- cious blood; </line>
			<line>How His kind- ness yet pur- sues me mor- tal tongue can nev- er tell, </line>
			<line>Clothed in flesh, till death shall loose me I can- not pro- claim it well. </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>O to grace how great a deb- tor dai- ly I'm con- strained to be! </line>
			<line>Let Thy good- ness, like a fet- ter, bind my wander- ing heart to Thee. </line>
			<line>Prone to wan- der, Lord, I feel it, prone to leave the God I love; </line>
			<line>Here's my heart, O take and seal it, seal it for Thy courts a- bove. </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>O that day when freed from sin- ning, I shall see Thy love- ly face; </line>
			<line>Clothed then in blood wa- shed lin- en how I'll sing Thy sove- reign grace; </line>
			<line>Come, my Lord, no long- er tar- ry, take my ran- somed soul a- way; </line>
			<line>Send thine an- gels now to car- ry me to realms of end- less day. </line>
		</verse>
	</verses>
</text>
