<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<text>
	<title>All Creatures of Our God and King</title>
	<author>Francis of Assissi</author>
	<year>1225</year>
	<meter name="null">
		<count>8</count>
		<count>8</count>
		<count>8</count>
		<count>8</count>
		<count>8</count>
		<count>8</count>
		<count>12</count>
	</meter>
	<verses>
		<verse>
			<line>All crea- tures of our God and King </line>
			<line>Lift up your voice and with us sing, </line>
			<line>Al- le- lu- ia! Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
			<line>Thou burn- ing sun with gold- en beam, </line>
			<line>Thou sil- ver moon with soft- er gleam! </line>
			<line>O- o praise him, O- o praise him, </line>
			<line>Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>Thou rush- ing wind that art so strong </line>
			<line>Ye clouds that sail in Heaven a- long, </line>
			<line>O- o praise Him! Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
			<line>Thou ris- ing moon, in praise re- joice, </line>
			<line>Ye lights of eve- ning, find a voice! </line>
			<line>O- o praise him, O- o praise him, </line>
			<line>Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>Thou flow- ing wa- ter, pure and clear, </line>
			<line>Make mu- sic for thy Lord to hear, </line>
			<line>O- o praise Him! Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
			<line>Thou fire so mas- ter- ful and bright, </line>
			<line>That giv- est man both warmth and light. </line>
			<line>O- o praise him, O- o praise him, </line>
			<line>Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>Dear mo- ther earth, who day by day </line>
			<line>Un- fol- dest bless- ings on our way, </line>
			<line>O- o praise Him! Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
			<line>The flowers and fruits that in thee grow, </line>
			<line>Let them His glo- ry al- so show. </line>
			<line>O- o praise him, O- o praise him, </line>
			<line>Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>And all ye men of ten- der heart, </line>
			<line>For- giv- ing o- thers, take your part, </line>
			<line>O- o sing ye! Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
			<line>Ye who long pain and sor- row bear, </line>
			<line>Praise God and on Him cast your care! </line>
			<line>O- o praise him, O- o praise him, </line>
			<line>Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>And thou most kind and gen- tle Death, </line>
			<line>Wait- ing to hush our lat- est breath, </line>
			<line>O- o praise Him! Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
			<line>Thou lead- est home the child of God, </line>
			<line>And Christ our Lord the way hath trod. </line>
			<line>O- o praise him, O- o praise him, </line>
			<line>Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
		</verse>
		<verse>
			<line>Let all things their Cre- a- tor bless, </line>
			<line>And wor- ship Him in hum- ble- ness, </line>
			<line>O- o praise Him! Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
			<line>Praise, praise the Fa- ther, praise the Son, </line>
			<line>And praise the Spir- it, Three in One! </line>
			<line>O- o praise him, O- o praise him, </line>
			<line>Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia, Al- le- lu- ia! </line>
		</verse>
	</verses>
</text>
